새벽 네 시 모니터 하나 켜놓고
At four in the morning, with one monitor turned on,
줄줄이 코드를 써 내려가
I write down lines and lines of code.
에러 백 개쯤 지우고 나면
After deleting about a hundred errors,
캐릭터 하나가 눈을 떠
A character opens its eyes.
아무도 모르는 이 작은 세계
This small world that no one knows,
내 손끝에서 태어나는 중
Is being born at my fingertips.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one step at a time,
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing through bug-ridden nights,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My very own game begins.
스프라이트 하나 그려 넣으면
When I draw in a single sprite,
작은 세상이 움직이잖아
The small world starts to move.
혼자서 다 해야 하는 밤이
The nights when I have to do everything alone
오히려 나를 웃게 만들어
Rather make me smile.
완성 버튼을 누르는 그날
The day I press the complete button,
온 세상이 플레이하게 될 거야
The whole world will play it.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one step at a time,
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing through bug-ridden nights,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My very own game begins.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
Creating dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one step at a time,
언젠가 누군가 플레이할 때
Someday, when someone plays it,
이 밤의 코드가 빛이 돼
The code of this night will become light.